Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art conservation department records, circa 1882-2019 COR0005.2.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Robert Scott Wiles records, 1971-1983; Series 4
  - Conservation of artworks records, 1971-1983; Series 4 Subseries 3
    - Kaemmerer, Frederick H. - Beach at Scheveningen, Holland, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Kainen, Jacob - Constantine, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Karafiol, Bernard - Summer, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Keith, William - By the Creek, Sonoma, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Kensett, John Frederick - Genesee River, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Kensett, John Frederick - Sketch of Mount Washington, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Knaus, L. - The Forester at Home, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo - Cows in Pasture, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Lever, Richard Hayley - Dawn, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Lhermitte, Leon Augustin - Washerwomen on the Banks of the Marne, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Luks, George - Woman with Black Cat, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - MacGiver, Loren - The Street, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - MacLeod, William - Maryland Heights: Seige of Harper's Ferry, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Maes - The Doctor's Visit, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Mathews, William T. - Presidential portraits (various), 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Maurer, Alfred - Woman, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Maurer, Alfred - Young Woman in a Kimono, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Maurer, Louis - Still Life "Trilby", 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Mauve, Anton - Return from Pasture, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Mayer, Frank B. - Leisure and Labor, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Melchers, Gari - Penelope, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Melchers, Gari - Portrait of Edward C. Walker, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Mengs, Anton Raphael - Adoration of the Shepherds, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Metcalf, Willard Leroy - May Night, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Metcalf, Willard Leory - River Landscape, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Millard - Mount Vernon, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Moeller, Louis Charles - The Disagreement, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Monet, Claude - The Willows of Vethueil, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Monticelli, Adolph - Corot and his Models, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Monticelli, Adolph - Return from the Hunt, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Monticelli, Adolph - Still Life, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Monticelli, Adolph - Testing the Fates, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Morris, George L.K. - Indian Composition, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Morse, S.F.B. - Joseph Gales, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Mount, William Sydney - The Long Story, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Mount, William Sydney - The Long Story, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Oakes, A.T. - Hudson River Landscape, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Oddie, Walter M. - Lake near Lenox, Mass, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Park, David - Sophomore Society, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Park, David - The Sun Bather, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Pater - The Camp, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Pater - The Departure, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Paxton, William - The House Maid, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Peale, Charles Wilson - Rebecca White, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Peale, James - Fruit, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Peale, Rembrandt - Jacque Henri Bernardin de Saint Pierre, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Peale, Rembrandt - Portrait of M. Lasteyrie, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Pena, Narcisse Diaz de la - In the Forest, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Pena, Narcisse Diaz de la - La Mare Aux Grenouilles, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Phillips, Ammi - Portrait of a Gentleman, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Phillips, Ammi - Portrait of a Lady, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Piazetta - Two Heads (The Flute Player), 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Picknell, William Lamb - Road to Concarneau, 1983; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Pissarro, Camille - The Seine at Paris, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Polk, Charles Peale - Mrs. Thomas Corcoran, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Polk, Charles Peale - Portrait of Thomas Corcoran, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Poor, Henry V. - Still Life with Apples and Pears, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Pratt, Mathew - Elizabeth Stevens Carle, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Preyer, J.W. - Fruit, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Raeburn, Sir Henry - Mrs Vere of Stonebyres, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Regnault, Henri - Head of a Moor, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Reinhart, Benjamin Franklin - The Emigrant Train Bedding Down for the Night, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Reinhart, Benjamin Franklin - The Emigrant Train Bedding Down for the Night, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - Remington, Frederick - Off the Range, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Renesse, Constantin - Convivality Near the Inn, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Ribera - Cafe Chautant, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Ribot, Theodule Augustin - The Orphan, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Richards, William Trost - On the Coast of New Jersey, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Robinson, Theodore - Layette, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Robinson, Theodore - Valley of the Seine from Giverny Heights, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Rothko, Mark - Mulberry and Brown, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Rousseua, Pierre Etienne Theodore - Paysage en Picardie, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Rousseau, Pierre Etienne Theodore - Sunlight, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - Rubens - Judgement of Midas, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Rundle, George - John Neagle, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Ryder, Albert Pinkham - The Stable, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Sage, Kay - A Finger on the Drum, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Sander, Ludwig - Scupperwong V, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Sargent, John Singer - Madame Edouard Pailleron, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Sargent, John Singer - Simplon Pass, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Savage, Edward - John Hancock and his Wife, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - Schaeffer, August - Hungarian Forest, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - Schreyer, Adolphe - The Watering Place, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Sheeler, L.R. - Dahlieas and Asters, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Sisley, A. - Marly le Roi, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Sloan, John - Yeats at Pepitas', 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Sonntag, William L. - Classic Italian Landscape, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Stanley, John Mix - The Disputed Shot, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Sterne, Maurice - After Lunch, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - Stevenson, A. Brockie - She's a Mighty Engine No. III, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Stuart, Gilbert - Portrait of George Washington, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Stuart, Gilbert - Portrait of Samuel Miles, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 173)
    - Stuart, Jane - Portrait of George Washington, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 174)
    - Sully, Thomas - Fanny Rundle, circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Sully, Thomas - James Madison, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Sully, Thomas - Portrait of Andrew Jackson, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - Sully, Thomas - William B. Wood as "Charles de Moor", 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - Tadema, Alma - Roman Youth Reading, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Tarbell, Edmund Charles - Josephine and Mercie, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Ter Borch, Gerard - Portraits of Marie Van Suchtelen and Gerhard Van Suchtelen, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Thayer, Abbott H. - Mount Monadnock, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - Troyon, Constant - Landscape with Figures, 1976; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Troyon, Constant - Moving with the Flock, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Trumbell, John - Mrs. Jonathan Mayhew Wainwright (Amelia Maria Phelps), circa 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Turner, J.M.W. - Boats Carrying out Anchors to Man-of-War-Ship, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Twachtman, John Henry - Spring Landscape, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Uhl, J. Jerome - Portrait of Grover Cleveland, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Ulke, Henry - Portrait of Ulysses S. Grant, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - Ulrich, Charles F. - In the Land of Promise, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - Unidentified Artist - The Belle Creole at New Orleans, 1982; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - Unidentified Artist - Charlotte Marsteller, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - Unidentified Artist - John A. Willson, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - Unidentified Artist - Portrait of Charles Carroll Glover, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Unidentified Artist - Portrait of John Scott Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Van der Helst, B. - Portrait of a Man, 1979; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - Van Goyen, Jan - View of Dordrecht from the North, 1977; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - Van Goyen, Jan - View of Rhenen, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Van Ruisdael, J. - Landscape with Fallen Tree, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Vanderlyn, John - Portrait of Zachary Taylor, 1972; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Vedder, Elihu - In Memoriam, 1973; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - Vibert, Jehan Georges - Untitled, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - Vigee-Lebrun, Louise-Elisabeth - Portrait of Madame Dubarry, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de - House and Poplars, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - Vonnoh, Robert William - Notre Dame de Paris, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Vonnoh, Robert William - Winter Landscape, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - Wall, William Guy - View of Cohoes, circa 1982; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - Walker, James - Review of Rhode Island and Maine Troops, 1981; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Webster, E.A. - Match Me if You Can, 1980; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Weir, J.A. - The Pet Bird, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - Whitredge, Thomas Worthington - Trout Brook in the Catskills, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 211)
    - Wright, Joseph - Benjamin Franklin, 1974; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Wyant, A.H. - View from Mount Mansfield, New York, 1971; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Yewell, George Henry - Young Boy, 1975; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - Ziem, F. - Street in Cairo, 1978; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 215)
    - Negatives of unidentified artwork conservation treatments, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folder 216)
    - Photographs of unidentified artwork conservation treatments, Undated; Series 4 Subseries 3 (Box 2, Folders 217-219)
- Dare Myers Hartwell records, 1982-2013, 2019; Series 5
  This series is arranged in 6 subseries: Hygrothermograph charts; Building exterior condition and restoration records; Conservation grants and financial records; Salon Dore restoration files; Nature Conservancy exhibition files; and Dare Myers Hartwell Conservation Consulting Services treatment reports
  This series contains records created by Corcoran staff conservator Dare Myers Hartwell in the course of her tenure at the Corcoran Gallery from 1983 to approximately 2014. Materials include hygrothermograph charts measuring temperature and relative humidity in the Corcoran Gallery, reports on restoration of the building's exterior, records and reports of various conservation grants, financial records, records related to the ongoing restoration of the Salon Dore, and condition reports for artworks returned from loan. The final subseries in this series contains reports and work undertaken by Hartwell as a contractor after she had retired. Records date from 1982-2019.
  - Hygrothermograph charts, 1982-2011; Series 5 Subseries 1
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    This subseries contains weekly hygrothermograph charts that recorded temperature and relative humidity in rooms of the Corcoran building, including the Archives, Art Storage, Cafe Storage, Conservation Lab, Salon Dore, and various galleries. The records date from 1982-2011, with gaps in 1984-1989, 1992-1998, and 2002-2006.
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1982 September-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1983 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1983 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1983 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1983 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1984 March-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1989 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1989 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1989 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1989 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1990 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1990 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1990 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1990 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1991 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1991 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1991 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1991 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1998 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1998 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1998 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1998 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1999 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1999 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1999 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 1999 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2000 February-August; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2001 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2001 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2001 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2001 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2002 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2002 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2002 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2002 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2006 December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2007 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2007 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2007 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2007 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2008 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2008 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2008 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2008 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2009 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2009 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2009 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2009 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2010 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2010 April-June; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2010 July-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2010 October-December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2011 January-March; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2011 April-May; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2011 June-July; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2011 August-September; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2011 October-November; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Hygrothermograph charts, 2011 December; Series 5 Subseries 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Building exterior condition and restoration records, 2000-2010; Series 5 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains records, reports, photographs, and CDs pertaining to restoration and preservation of the exterior of the Corcoran Gallery's Flagg building. Records date from 2000-2010.
    - Interior Stonework, 2013; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Column Cleaning Bridge, 2009; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Cleaning Building-Interior Stonework Vestibule, Atrium Columns, Rotunda, 2005-2008; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Column Cleaning, 2005; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Integrated Conservation Resources, Inc., 1997-1998; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Building Condition Photos Made by Lane Burritt, 2006; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Condition Survey Building Exterior, 2006; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Exterior Condition Assessment, 2006-2007; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - John Milner Field Report, 2008 August; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folders 9-10)
    - Masonry Facade Restoration Final Report, 2009; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Facade Restoration During Construction, 2012; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Bronze Grilles, 2008; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Bronze Window Grills, 2009; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Interior Building Metalwork, 1997; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Roof Restoration, 2008; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Roof Restoration Images, 2009; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Roof, 2008; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Roof, Flagg Building Griffins, Ornamental Cresting & Cast Iron Railing Treatment Report, 2010; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Roof, Flagg Building Griffins, Ornamental Copper Cresting & Cast Iron Railing Treatment Notes, 2008-2009; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Roof, Flagg Building Griffins Technical Report, 2009; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Smithsonian Museum Conservation Institute - Technical Examination, Especially Radiography of W.H. Mullins' Griffins from the Roof of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 2009 September 9; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Bronze Doors, 17th & NY Ave, 2000; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - CGA Drawings from Oehrlein & Assoc., Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 25)
    - Corcoran Griffins X-Ray Images, 2009 July 7; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 26)
    - Presentation Images, 2008 July 31; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 27)
    - Corcoran Window Grilles During Treatment by Wilson Conservation, 2009 April 14; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 28)
    - Corcoran Roof Presentation JMA, 2007 June 20; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 29)
    - JMA Corcoran Ext Survey July Update .pdf, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 30)
    - Images at Vatica Corcoran, 2009 May 5; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 31)
    - Roof Renovation Project Photos # 1-722 on 3 Disks Copied, 2010 August 17; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 32)
    - Facade Treatment Photos 1 of 2, 2008 December; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 33)
    - Facade Treatment Photos 2 of 2, 2008 December; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 34)
    - Corcoran Gallery Renovation Photos, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 35)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Condition Assessment, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 36)
    - CGA Building Facade & Interior, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 37)
    - CGA Building Roof, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 6, Cd 38)
  - Conservation grants and financial records, 1984-2013; Series 5 Subseries 3
    This subseries is arranged by grant organization, then chronologically, followed by general financial and funding files.